(Sheldon:)Oh. How much does it cost
to get them off my lap?
(James:)No. Something about a convention.
Oh, right! Well...
(Sheldon:)...my friends and I couldn't
get into Comic-Con this year,
(Sheldon:)and I was trying to start
my own convention,
(Sheldon:)and I was going to ask
if you would be a panelist.
(James:)Why don't you and your friends
come to Comic-Can with me?
(Howard:)-Really?
-Of course.
(James:)And San Diego is
right across the border
from my favourite city on Earth,
Tijuana...
(James:)...where I'm taking you
every night!
Ay-ay-ay.
Ay-ay-ay, bang-bang.
(James:)So, Beau Bridges
is on my shoulders,
(James:)and Jeff Bridges is
on Marlon Brando's shoulders,
(James:)and remember, we do not have
permission to be in the pool.
Hey! Sheldon, wake up!
(James:)Angie Dickinson is about to
sic the dogs on us,
(James:)and I go under the water and
Marlon goes under the water,
(James:)and the water raises
about two feet
(James:)and sloshes all over her patio,
(James:)and the dogs freak out
and run like hell,
(James:)then we run like hell....
Oh, boy!
(James:)That was a lot of fun.
(Sheldon:)Who's Angie Dickinson?